
const questions = [
    {
        question: "Take the sum of 3 scores and 5 dozen from a gross",
        answers: {
            a: 24,
            b: 44,
            c: 54,
            d: 64
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Change 5 weeks 4 days to days.",
        answers: {
            a: "33 days",
            b: "39 days",
            c: "101 days",
            d: "304 days"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "A father shared N480 between his two sons, Ade and Benson.  If Benson gets N40 more than Ade, how much did Benson get?",
        answers: {
            a: 20000,
            b: 2000,
            c: 800,
            d: 8
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: " The volume of a room is 240 square cm, if the length is 10m and the height is 4m, find the breadth.",
        answers: {
            a: 6,
            b: 8,
            c: 7,
            d: 5
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Simplify and write your answers in Roman numerals.  One-third of LXVI.",
        answers: {
            a: "XX",
            b: "XXI",
            c: "XXII",
            d: "XXIII"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Express in figures: Eight million, eight hundred and eight",
        answers: {
            a:8018818,
            b:80000808,
            c:8088880,
            d:80880880
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "How many hectares can be found in a plot of land measuring 400m long and 300m wide?",
        answers: {
            a: "12ha",
            b: "120ha",
            c: "1200ha",
            d: "12000ha"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "A ladder 25m long leans against a wall. The top of the ladder from the ground is 24m. What is the length of the base resting on the level ground from the wall?",
        answers: {
            a: "8m",
            b: "7m",
            c: "16m",
            d: "20m"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Three brothers shared a sum of N2,520 in the proportion 1:2:4.  How much did the older get?",
        answers: {
            a: "N 360",
            b: "N 630",
            c: "N 720",
            d: "N 1440"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },

    {
        question: "In a mixed school, 130 of the pupils are girls. If there are 128 boys, how many pupils are there altogether?",
        answers: {
            a: 216,
            b: 226,
            c: 258,
            d: 288
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    }
]	

